<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Country Music on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/country-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Country Music on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/country-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Classic Song Will Make You Want to Roll It On Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-classic-song-will-make-you-want-to-roll-it-on-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-classic-song-will-make-you-want-to-roll-it-on-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever find yourself humming along to a classic song that you just can&amp;rsquo;t get out of your head? That&amp;rsquo;s how we feel about the song &amp;ldquo;Roll It On Home&amp;rdquo; by Eddie Rabbitt This classic country song has been around for decades and is still beloved by many
Background of the Song &amp;ldquo;Roll It On Home&amp;rdquo; was released in 180 as the third single from Eddie Rabbitt&amp;rsquo;s album Horizon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Believe What Chris Young Says in His New Song &#39;Gettin&#39; You Home&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-never-believe-what-chris-young-says-in-his-new-song-gettin-you-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-never-believe-what-chris-young-says-in-his-new-song-gettin-you-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Chris Young is a country music star who has been making music for over a decade His latest single, “Gettin’ You Home”, is a heartfelt love song that has become a fan-favorite In this blog post, we will explore the lyrics of the song, analyze its themes, and discuss the impact it has had on listeners
Introduction to Chris Young Chris Young is an American country music singer-songwriter from Murfreesboro, Tennessee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Country Star Jimmie Allen Just Said in His Down Home Lyrics!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-country-star-jimmie-allen-just-said-in-his-down-home-lyrics-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-country-star-jimmie-allen-just-said-in-his-down-home-lyrics-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Jimmie Allen and His Music Jimmie Allen is a country music superstar who has been taking the music world by storm His debut single, &amp;ldquo;Best Shot,&amp;rdquo; reached number one on the US Country Airplay chart and was the first song by a black artist to do so He has since released several more hit singles, including &amp;ldquo;Make Me Want To&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;21&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;This Is Us&amp;rdquo; His music is a mix of traditional country and modern pop, and he has been praised for his down-home lyrics and catchy melodies</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Be Singing Along to This Heartwarming Tennessee Mountain Home Song!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-be-singing-along-to-this-heartwarming-tennessee-mountain-home-song-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-be-singing-along-to-this-heartwarming-tennessee-mountain-home-song-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
I Introduction Are you looking for a song that will make you feel warm and fuzzy inside? Look no further than this Tennessee Mountain Home song! This heartwarming track is sure to have you singing along in no time
II. Background of the Song This song was written by the late country music legend, Dolly Parton. She wrote it in honor of her beloved Tennessee home and the people who live there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Classic Country Song Will Make You Long for the Cotton Fields Back Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-classic-country-song-will-make-you-long-for-the-cotton-fields-back-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-classic-country-song-will-make-you-long-for-the-cotton-fields-back-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Classic country music is a genre of music that has been around for many generations It is often characterized by its simple lyrics, heartfelt stories, and catchy melodies One classic country song that stands out is “Cotton Fields Back Home” by Bill Anderson This song is a perfect example of a classic country song, and it will make you long for the cotton fields back home
Definition of a Classic Country Song A classic country song is typically a song that was written and recorded in the 150s and 160s.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
