<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>College Basketball on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/college-basketball/</link>
    <description>Recent content in College Basketball on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/college-basketball/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Surprising Team Just Made it Into the Big Ten Men&#39;s Basketball Tournament Bracket!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-surprising-team-just-made-it-into-the-big-ten-men-s-basketball-tournament-bracket-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-surprising-team-just-made-it-into-the-big-ten-men-s-basketball-tournament-bracket-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is one of the most highly anticipated events of the college basketball season Every year, teams from the Big Ten conference compete for the championship title in a thrilling and exciting tournament This year, there is an unexpected surprise that has everyone talking: a surprise team has made it into the tournament bracket!
Overview of the Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is an annual event that takes place in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe Who Just Won the Big Ten Men&#39;s Basketball Tournament 2022 Bracket!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-who-just-won-the-big-ten-men-s-basketball-tournament-2022-bracket-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-who-just-won-the-big-ten-men-s-basketball-tournament-2022-bracket-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is one of the most prestigious and competitive tournaments in college basketball Every year, teams from the Big Ten Conference compete to determine the champion of the conference This year, the 2022 Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament was an exciting one, with the winner being a surprise to many
Overview of Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is an annual event that takes place every year in March It is a single-elimination tournament featuring the top teams from the Big Ten Conference The winner of the tournament is crowned the Big Ten Champion and earns an automatic bid to the NCAA Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
