<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Ohio&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/ohio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ohio&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/ohio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Affordable These Homes Are - Check Out Kinsman, Ohio Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-these-homes-are-check-out-kinsman-ohio-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-these-homes-are-check-out-kinsman-ohio-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an affordable place to live that still offers plenty of amenities? Kinsman, Ohio is the perfect place for those looking for a great deal on a home Located just a few miles outside of Cleveland, Kinsman offers a great quality of life at an unbeatable price
Overview of Kinsman, Ohio Kinsman is a small town in Trumbull County, Ohio It is home to around 2,300 people and is located just a few miles outside of Cleveland Kinsman is known for its rural charm, with plenty of green space and open fields It is also known for its friendly people and strong sense of community</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Cheap These Houses in Kinsman, Ohio Are!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-cheap-these-houses-in-kinsman-ohio-are-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-cheap-these-houses-in-kinsman-ohio-are-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Cheap These Houses in Kinsman, Ohio Are! Are you looking for a place to call home that doesn&amp;rsquo;t break the bank? Kinsman, Ohio, might be the perfect place for you In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of living in Kinsman and why houses in the area are so affordable
I Introduction Kinsman is a small village in Trumbull County, Ohio. It&amp;rsquo;s located about 25 miles northwest of Youngstown and about 80 miles southeast of Cleveland.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe the Incredible Homes Available Now in Middlefield, Ohio!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-incredible-homes-available-now-in-middlefield-ohio-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-the-incredible-homes-available-now-in-middlefield-ohio-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a place to call home? Middlefield, Ohio is a great place to live and there are some incredible homes available now! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the location and climate of Middlefield, Ohio and the incredible homes available now
Overview of Middlefield, Ohio Middlefield, Ohio is located in Geauga County, about 30 miles east of Cleveland It&amp;rsquo;s a small town with a population of about 3,000 people The town is surrounded by beautiful rolling hills and farmland The climate in Middlefield is mild, with warm summers and cold winters The town has a variety of amenities, including a library, a recreation center, and a variety of restaurants and shops</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Affordable Homes in Damascus, Ohio Are Right Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-homes-in-damascus-ohio-are-right-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-homes-in-damascus-ohio-are-right-now-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Affordable Homes in Damascus, Ohio Are Right Now! Are you looking to buy a home in a small town with a strong sense of community? Look no further than Damascus, Ohio! Homes in Damascus, Ohio are surprisingly affordable, and they offer a great quality of life Here&amp;rsquo;s why you should consider buying a home in Damascus, Ohio
Reasons why homes in Damascus, Ohio are so affordable Damascus, Ohio is a small town with a population of just over 1,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
