<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>K-pop on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/k-pop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in K-pop on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/k-pop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Lisa from Blackpink Did in 2020 - How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lisa-from-blackpink-did-in-2020-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lisa-from-blackpink-did-in-2020-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Lisa from Blackpink Did in 2020 - How You Like That! Introduction 2020 has been an unforgettable year for many, but for Lisa from Blackpink it has been a year of unprecedented success In 2020, Lisa achieved a number of impressive milestones, including releasing her own solo single, collaborating with Lady Gaga, and appearing in a movie Read on to learn more about what Lisa from Blackpink did in 2020 and the impact of her accomplishments</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Jisoo Did With Her &#39;How You Like That&#39; Poster!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-jisoo-did-with-her-how-you-like-that-poster-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-jisoo-did-with-her-how-you-like-that-poster-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction BLACKPINK&amp;rsquo;s Jisoo has been making waves with her latest solo project, the &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; poster Fans have been amazed by her creative transformation of the poster, which has become an iconic piece of art In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at Jisoo&amp;rsquo;s artistic process and the impact of her creative design
Overview of Jisoo’s ‘How You Like That’ Poster Jisoo&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; poster has quickly become an iconic image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>songYou Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Listen to Blackpink&#39;s New Song!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/songyou-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-blackpink-s-new-song-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/songyou-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-listen-to-blackpink-s-new-song-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is a South Korean girl group that has quickly become one of the most popular and successful K-pop groups in the world They have released a new song, and it&amp;rsquo;s sure to be a hit! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at what makes this song so special and why you should give it a listen
Definition of Blackpink Blackpink is a four-member girl group that debuted in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Jisoo Just Did with &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-jisoo-just-did-with-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-jisoo-just-did-with-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink Jisoo is a South Korean singer, songwriter, and actress who is part of the K-pop girl group Blackpink She has recently made headlines for her latest accomplishment with her song ‘How You Like That’ In this blog post, we will be discussing what ‘How You Like That’ is, what Blackpink Jisoo achieved with the song, and how the public reacted to her accomplishment
Background Information Blackpink was formed in 2016 and consists of four members: Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Did With &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Blackpink and Their New Single &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; Blackpink is a four-member girl group from South Korea that has been gaining international attention since their debut in 2016 The group consists of Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa Their latest single, “How You Like That”, was released on June 26th, 2020 and has already taken the world by storm
Overview of the Music Video and Its Record-Breaking Success The music video for “How You Like That” has set numerous records since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When BTS and BLACKPINK Performed &#39;How You Like That&#39; Together!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-bts-and-blackpink-performed-how-you-like-that-together-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-bts-and-blackpink-performed-how-you-like-that-together-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction K-pop fans around the world were in for a real treat when two of the biggest groups in the industry, BTS and BLACKPINK, came together to perform their hit single &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; for the first time ever This collaboration was highly anticipated and fans were eager to see what the two groups had in store
Overview of BTS and BLACKPINK BTS is one of the most popular K-pop groups in the world, with millions of fans around the globe The group consists of seven members, RM, Jin, Suga, J-Hope, Jimin, V, and Jungkook, and they are known for their unique blend of hip-hop, pop, and EDM BLACKPINK is another popular K-pop group, consisting of four members, Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa The group has been gaining international recognition for their catchy pop songs and their powerful stage presence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When We Unwrapped This Jisoo Poster - How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-unwrapped-this-jisoo-poster-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-unwrapped-this-jisoo-poster-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A few weeks ago, my friends and I had the amazing opportunity to unwrap a Jisoo poster from BLACKPINK We had been fans of the group for a while, and were so excited to get our hands on this special item We couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what it looked like and what kind of quality it was
Background of Jisoo and BLACKPINK Jisoo is a member of the K-pop girl group BLACKPINK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Behind This Blackpink &#39;How You Like That&#39; Poster!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-behind-this-blackpink-how-you-like-that-poster-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-behind-this-blackpink-how-you-like-that-poster-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of the K-pop girl group Blackpink? If so, you may have seen their latest hit song “How You Like That” and the accompanying poster But do you know what’s behind the poster? Read on to find out!
Background Information Blackpink is a four-member K-pop girl group that debuted in 2016 under YG Entertainment. They have released several hit singles, including “Kill This Love”, “Boombayah”, and “Ddu-Du Ddu-Du”, and have become one of the most popular K-pop girl groups in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Black Pink Just Did with &#39;How Do You Like That&#39; - You Have to See It Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-black-pink-just-did-with-how-do-you-like-that-you-have-to-see-it-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-black-pink-just-did-with-how-do-you-like-that-you-have-to-see-it-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Black Pink is a South Korean girl group that has been making waves in the K-pop scene since their debut in 2016 Recently, they released their highly anticipated single, &amp;lsquo;How Do You Like That&amp;rsquo;, and the accompanying music video has been making headlines all over the world In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll be taking a look at the music video and exploring the impact it has had on the K-pop world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Move Will Make You Dance Like Blackpink in &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-move-will-make-you-dance-like-blackpink-in-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-move-will-make-you-dance-like-blackpink-in-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of the K-Pop girl group Blackpink and their hit song &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo;? If so, you may be wondering how you can dance like the members of Blackpink in the song Well, we&amp;rsquo;ve got some great news for you! We&amp;rsquo;ve discovered one move that, when mastered, will make you dance like Blackpink in no time!
Overview of Blackpink&amp;rsquo;s Song &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; Blackpink&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; is a high-energy song that features a catchy hook and a powerful beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What BLACKPINK Just Did with &#39;How Do You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-how-do-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-did-with-how-do-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction BLACKPINK is a K-pop girl group that has taken the world by storm Since their debut in 2016, they have become one of the most popular girl groups in the world, with millions of fans around the globe Their latest single, &amp;ldquo;How Do You Like That,&amp;rdquo; is a powerful and catchy song that has made waves in the music industry In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore what BLACKPINK did with &amp;ldquo;How Do You Like That&amp;rdquo; and why it had such an impact</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>songYou Won&#39;t Believe How Much People Are Loving This Black Pink Song!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/songyou-won-t-believe-how-much-people-are-loving-this-black-pink-song-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/songyou-won-t-believe-how-much-people-are-loving-this-black-pink-song-/</guid>
      <description>Black Pink is Taking Over the Music Industry Black Pink is a South Korean girl group that has been making waves in the music industry since their debut in 2016 The group consists of four members: Jisoo, Jennie, Lisa, and Rosé They are known for their unique style of music, which blends elements of hip-hop, R&amp;amp;B, and EDM
Popularity of their Song Black Pink&amp;rsquo;s latest single, &amp;ldquo;As If It&amp;rsquo;s Your Last,&amp;rdquo; has been a huge hit with fans around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kim Jisoo Drops a Banger That You Can&#39;t Help But Love</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/kim-jisoo-drops-a-banger-that-you-can-t-help-but-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/kim-jisoo-drops-a-banger-that-you-can-t-help-but-love/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Kim Jisoo, a South Korean singer, songwriter, and actress, recently released her latest banger, and it&amp;rsquo;s quickly become a fan favorite From the catchy beat to the meaningful lyrics, Kim Jisoo&amp;rsquo;s banger is sure to be a hit Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what makes this banger so special
Background on Kim Jisoo Kim Jisoo is a member of the South Korean girl group Blackpink She made her solo debut in 2020 with the release of her single &amp;ldquo;Solo&amp;rdquo; Since then, she&amp;rsquo;s been making waves in the K-pop industry with her powerful vocals and incredible stage presence</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lalisa Manoban&#39;s New Song &#39;How You Like That&#39; Will Leave You Speechless!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lalisa-manoban-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-will-leave-you-speechless-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lalisa-manoban-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-will-leave-you-speechless-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lalisa Manoban, also known as Lisa, is a Thai singer and dancer who is part of the K-Pop group BLACKPINK On June 26th, 2020, she released her solo single, &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo;, which has been met with critical acclaim and commercial success This song is sure to leave you speechless!
Overview of Lalisa Manoban&amp;rsquo;s Song &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; The song &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; is an upbeat and energetic track that is sure to get you on your feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Rose From Blackpink Looks Like in This Photo!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-rose-from-blackpink-looks-like-in-this-photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-rose-from-blackpink-looks-like-in-this-photo-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
I Introduction A Background information Rose, or Park Chaeyoung, is a member of the South Korean girl group Blackpink Since the group&amp;rsquo;s debut in 2016, Rose has been gaining recognition for her talent and beauty Recently, a photo of Rose has been circulating on the internet, and people have been reacting to it in a variety of ways
B. Thesis statement The photo of Rose has been met with both positive and negative reactions from fans and non-fans alike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
