<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When These Jackers Tried to Enter This Home - Listen to the Lyrics Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-these-jackers-tried-to-enter-this-home-listen-to-the-lyrics-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-these-jackers-tried-to-enter-this-home-listen-to-the-lyrics-now-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happened When These Jackers Tried to Enter This Home - Listen to the Lyrics Now! Have you ever heard of the song &amp;ldquo;Jackers Tried to Enter This Home&amp;rdquo; by the artist KAAN? If not, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a real treat! This song tells a thrilling story of a home invasion gone wrong In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at what happened when the jackers tried to enter this home, analyze the lyrics, and discuss the significance of the song</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Russell Bufalino&#39;s Wife Has Been Up To!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-russell-bufalino-s-wife-has-been-up-to-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-russell-bufalino-s-wife-has-been-up-to-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Russell Bufalino is a well-known figure in organized crime circles He is the former boss of the powerful Bufalino crime family But what many people don&amp;rsquo;t know is that his wife, Mary Bufalino, has been quietly working behind the scenes to make a difference in the world In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the charitable works Mary Bufalino has been involved in
Background of Russell Bufalino Russell Bufalino was born in Pittston, Pennsylvania in 103.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shocking Discovery: Home Invasion Rocks Peaceful Sandy Springs Neighborhood!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/shocking-discovery-home-invasion-rocks-peaceful-sandy-springs-neighborhood-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/shocking-discovery-home-invasion-rocks-peaceful-sandy-springs-neighborhood-/</guid>
      <description>, IV Safety Tips
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s a sad day in Sandy Springs, Georgia A peaceful, suburban neighborhood was rocked by a home invasion last week, leaving the community shaken and looking for answers The incident has raised questions about safety in the area, and has left many residents feeling vulnerable and scared
Details of the Home Invasion The incident occurred on a Tuesday night, when two men broke into a home in the neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
