<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Language Learning on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/language-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Language Learning on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/language-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When This Person Tried to Say &#39;I Want to Go Home&#39; in Spanish!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-to-say-i-want-to-go-home-in-spanish-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-to-say-i-want-to-go-home-in-spanish-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to learn a foreign language? Have you ever wanted to travel to a foreign country and be able to communicate with the locals? If so, you can certainly relate to this person&amp;rsquo;s experience when they tried to say &amp;ldquo;I want to go home&amp;rdquo; in Spanish
Background on Spanish Language Spanish is a Romance language spoken by about 500 million people around the world. It is the official language of 21 countries and is the second most spoken language in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Say &#39;I Am Home&#39; in Spanish!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-say-i-am-home-in-spanish-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-say-i-am-home-in-spanish-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever been curious about what happens when you say &amp;ldquo;I am home&amp;rdquo; in Spanish? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the reasons why you should say &amp;ldquo;I am home&amp;rdquo; in Spanish, as well as the benefits that come with doing so
Reasons to Say &amp;lsquo;I Am Home&amp;rsquo; in Spanish There are a few reasons why you should say &amp;ldquo;I am home&amp;rdquo; in Spanish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You&#39;ll Never Believe the Simple Way to Say &#39;Go Home&#39; in Spanish!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-never-believe-the-simple-way-to-say-go-home-in-spanish-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-ll-never-believe-the-simple-way-to-say-go-home-in-spanish-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Are you looking for a simple way to say &amp;lsquo;Go Home&amp;rsquo; in Spanish? Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner Spanish learner or an advanced speaker, you&amp;rsquo;ll be amazed to learn the easiest way to express this phrase to someone Read on to find out!
II Common Ways to Say &amp;lsquo;Go Home&amp;rsquo; in Spanish The Spanish phrase for &amp;lsquo;Go Home&amp;rsquo; is &amp;lsquo;Vete a casa&amp;rsquo;. This is the most common way to say it and is used in both formal and informal settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Help You Instantly Speak Spanish to Go Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-speak-spanish-to-go-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-help-you-instantly-speak-spanish-to-go-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a way to quickly learn Spanish so you can go home and start speaking it? If so, then this one simple trick will help you do just that! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide an overview of the trick, as well as step-by-step instructions on how to use it
Purpose of the Article The purpose of this article is to provide a simple and effective way to learn Spanish quickly so you can start speaking it in no time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Heartwarming Way to Say &#39;Welcome Home&#39; in Spanish!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-heartwarming-way-to-say-welcome-home-in-spanish-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-heartwarming-way-to-say-welcome-home-in-spanish-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Are you looking for a special way to say “Welcome Home” in Spanish? You’ve come to the right place! Whether you’re welcoming a family member, friend, or visitor, there are plenty of warm and welcoming phrases in Spanish to show your hospitality Read on to discover some of the most common and heartfelt ways to say “Welcome Home” in Spanish
II Common Phrases for Welcoming Someone Home When welcoming someone home in Spanish, it’s important to remember that the phrase you choose will depend on the relationship you have with the person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Say &#39;How You Like That&#39; in Korean!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-say-how-you-like-that-in-korean-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-say-how-you-like-that-in-korean-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever heard the phrase “How You Like That”? It’s a popular phrase used in English, but did you know that you can also say it in Korean? This blog post will give you a step-by-step guide to saying “How You Like That” in Korean, as well as the benefits of knowing how to do so
Definition of “How You Like That” The phrase “How You Like That” is used to express surprise, admiration, or approval It is often used as an exclamation of joy or excitement</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Will Have You Speaking Spanish Fluently and Going Home in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-have-you-speaking-spanish-fluently-and-going-home-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-will-have-you-speaking-spanish-fluently-and-going-home-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you ready to become fluent in Spanish? With this one simple trick, you can be speaking Spanish fluently and going home in no time! Let’s take a look at what it takes to become fluent in Spanish, the trick, and the benefits of achieving fluency
Definition of Fluency Fluency in any language is defined as the ability to understand, read, write, and speak the language with ease. It is often the goal of language learners to reach a level of fluency in order to communicate effectively in the language.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
