<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Origami on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/origami/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Origami on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/origami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Origami Trick Will Have You Flying High - Learn How to Make a Jet!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-origami-trick-will-have-you-flying-high-learn-how-to-make-a-jet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-origami-trick-will-have-you-flying-high-learn-how-to-make-a-jet-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Origami is an ancient art form that has been practiced for centuries It is a fun and creative way to express yourself and make something from nothing With a few simple folds and some patience, you can make amazing objects from paper In this blog post, we will show you how to make a paper jet using origami Read on to learn the step-by-step instructions and the benefits of learning origami</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Teach You How to Make Airplane Paper in Just Minutes!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-airplane-paper-in-just-minutes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-airplane-paper-in-just-minutes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Airplane Paper Airplane paper, also known as origami paper, is a type of paper that can be folded and manipulated into a variety of shapes It is often used to create models of airplanes, animals, and other objects Learning how to make airplane paper is a great way to practice your origami skills and create beautiful, intricate designs
Benefits of Learning How to Make Airplane Paper Learning how to make airplane paper can be a fun and rewarding experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Amazing Trick Will Have You Folding Airplanes in No Time - Learn How to Make Origami Airplanes Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-amazing-trick-will-have-you-folding-airplanes-in-no-time-learn-how-to-make-origami-airplanes-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-amazing-trick-will-have-you-folding-airplanes-in-no-time-learn-how-to-make-origami-airplanes-now-/</guid>
      <description>This Amazing Trick Will Have You Folding Airplanes in No Time Are you looking for a fun and creative way to pass the time? Look no further than origami airplanes! Origami is the art of folding paper into various shapes and figures, and it is a great way to express your creativity and have a little fun In this blog post, we will discuss the basics of origami airplanes, the materials you need to get started, and the steps for making them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make a Realistic Origami Fighter Jet!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-realistic-origami-fighter-jet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-easy-it-is-to-make-a-realistic-origami-fighter-jet-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe How Easy It Is To Make a Realistic Origami Fighter Jet! Origami is a fun and creative way to make all kinds of shapes and objects out of paper It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to pass the time and make something beautiful without having to spend a lot of money Making an origami fighter jet is a great project for anyone who loves making things out of paper Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to making a realistic origami fighter jet</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Incredible Trick Will Teach You How to Make the Best Origami Paper Plane Ever!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-incredible-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-the-best-origami-paper-plane-ever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-incredible-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-make-the-best-origami-paper-plane-ever-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Origami is a wonderful art form that has been around for centuries It is a great way to express creativity and can be a great way to spend quality time with friends and family Making origami paper planes is a fun and exciting way to get involved in origami In this blog post, we will discuss the steps and benefits of learning how to make the best paper plane</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You an Expert at Making Eagle Paper Planes!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-an-expert-at-making-eagle-paper-planes-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-an-expert-at-making-eagle-paper-planes-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and easy way to make a paper plane? Look no further than the Eagle Paper Plane! This fun paper plane is easy to make and provides hours of entertainment In this blog post, we will discuss the definition of an Eagle Paper Plane, the benefits of learning how to make one, and the steps to create your own Eagle Paper Plane
Definition of an Eagle Paper Plane An Eagle Paper Plane is a type of paper plane that has wings that are angled outwards and a tail that is angled downwards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
