<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Humor&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/humor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humor&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/humor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Homer Simpson Does After Seeing This Picture!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-does-after-seeing-this-picture-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-does-after-seeing-this-picture-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction We all know and love Homer Simpson, the lovable, bumbling father of the Simpson family He&amp;rsquo;s always getting himself into hilarious hijinks, but recently he encountered something that left him completely speechless
II Description of the Picture The picture in question is a photo of a giant doughnut It&amp;rsquo;s a classic glazed doughnut, with a light golden-brown color and a generous helping of sprinkles It&amp;rsquo;s so big that it could easily feed a family of four</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When Homer Simpson Met This Bar Meme!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-homer-simpson-met-this-bar-meme-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-homer-simpson-met-this-bar-meme-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We all know Homer Simpson, the beloved protagonist of the long-running animated sitcom The Simpsons But did you know that he recently had a chance meeting with one of the internet&amp;rsquo;s most famous memes? In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the details of their meeting and the impact it had on both Homer and the Bar Meme
Background of Homer Simpson and the Bar Meme Homer Simpson is a cartoon character who has been a part of American culture for over 30 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Homer Simpson Did With Donuts - You&#39;ll Be Shocked!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-did-with-donuts-you-ll-be-shocked-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-did-with-donuts-you-ll-be-shocked-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Homer Simpson is a beloved character from the long-running animated television show, The Simpsons He is known for his love of donuts, often eating them in large quantities Recently, however, Homer has taken his love of donuts to a new level You won&amp;rsquo;t believe what he did with donuts - you&amp;rsquo;ll be shocked!
Homer Simpson&amp;rsquo;s Unique Use of Donuts Homer Simpson has found a way to use donuts in a creative and unique way He has used donuts to build a variety of structures such as a donut castle, a donut car, and even a donut house He has also used donuts to create art, such as a donut mural on the side of a building His creative use of donuts has had a huge impact on the people of Springfield, inspiring them to think outside the box and use donuts in new and exciting ways</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Hilarious &#39;I&#39;m Home Alone&#39; Meme Will Have You Laughing Out Loud!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-hilarious-i-m-home-alone-meme-will-have-you-laughing-out-loud-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-hilarious-i-m-home-alone-meme-will-have-you-laughing-out-loud-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you spend any amount of time online, chances are you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Home Alone&amp;rdquo; meme This hilarious meme has been making its rounds on the internet for years and is sure to have you laughing out loud In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a deeper look at the origins and meaning of the &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Home Alone&amp;rdquo; meme, as well as some of the most popular examples
Overview of the “I’m Home Alone” Meme The &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m Home Alone&amp;rdquo; meme is a humorous image macro that features a picture of actor Macaulay Culkin in the 1990 film Home Alone The image is usually accompanied by text that expresses a feeling of excitement or joy in being alone The meme is often used to express a sense of freedom or relief at being able to do whatever one wants without anyone else around</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When She Put On That Bucket Hat!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-put-on-that-bucket-hat-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-put-on-that-bucket-hat-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bucket hats have been around for decades, but they&amp;rsquo;ve recently become a popular fashion trend From celebrities to everyday people, everyone is trying out the trend But what happens when someone decides to take the plunge and wear a bucket hat for the first time?
Background Information Bucket hats have been around since the early 100s, but they weren&amp;rsquo;t popular until the 180s. Since then, they&amp;rsquo;ve been seen on everyone from hip-hop artists to college students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When Chicken Came Home to Roost!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-chicken-came-home-to-roost-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-chicken-came-home-to-roost-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A Background Information
The phrase “when the chicken comes home to roost” is a popular idiom that is often used to refer to the consequences of one’s actions It is believed to have originated in the early 19th century and has been used by a variety of authors, including Mark Twain and William Faulkner The phrase is used to illustrate the idea that the consequences of one’s actions will eventually come back to haunt them</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When This Homer in Bed Meme Comes to Life!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-homer-in-bed-meme-comes-to-life-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-homer-in-bed-meme-comes-to-life-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Homer in Bed meme is one of the most recognizable memes in the world It features Homer Simpson, the lovable father of the Simpson family, lying in bed with a look of utter exhaustion The meme has been around for years and has been used to represent various feelings of exhaustion and frustration But what would happen if the Homer in Bed meme came to life?
Background on the Homer in Bed Meme The Homer in Bed meme originated from an episode of the popular animated sitcom The Simpsons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Homer Simpson Falls Asleep in This Hilarious Meme!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-homer-simpson-falls-asleep-in-this-hilarious-meme-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-homer-simpson-falls-asleep-in-this-hilarious-meme-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Homer Simpson is a classic cartoon character from the hit show The Simpsons He is known for his bumbling antics, his catchphrases, and his love of donuts Recently, a hilarious meme has been circulating the internet featuring Homer Simpson falling asleep In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the meme, analyze its visual elements, themes, and humor, and discuss its impact
Overview of Homer Simpson Homer Simpson is a middle-aged man who works at the Springfield Nuclear Power Plant He is married to Marge Simpson, with whom he has three children: Bart, Lisa, and Maggie Homer is known for his love of beer, donuts, and television He is also known for his frequent bumbling and his catchphrases, such as &amp;ldquo;D&amp;rsquo;oh!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When These Nudists Tried Filming a Home Video!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-these-nudists-tried-filming-a-home-video-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-these-nudists-tried-filming-a-home-video-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happened When These Nudists Tried Filming a Home Video! Have you ever wondered what it would be like to film a home video while being completely nude? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what these nudists decided to do
The Preparation The nudists prepared for their home video by setting up a camera on a tripod and covering the floor with a large tarp. They also set up a few props and a few lights to create a more professional look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When This Kid Tries a Home Alone Electric Shock Prank!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-kid-tries-a-home-alone-electric-shock-prank-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-kid-tries-a-home-alone-electric-shock-prank-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever seen the classic movie Home Alone where Macaulay Culkin sets up an electric shock prank on the two burglars? Well, this kid decided to try it out for himself and the results were hilarious!
Set Up To set up the prank, the kid gathered a few materials. He needed a door, a battery, some wires, a light bulb, and a few other items. After gathering the materials, he set up the prank by connecting the wires to the battery and the door handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When This Person Tried Making McDonalds at Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-making-mcdonalds-at-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-making-mcdonalds-at-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to recreate McDonalds at home? Well, one brave soul decided to take on the challenge and see if it was possible Read on to find out what happened when they tried to make McDonalds at home!
Steps Taken to Recreate McDonalds at Home The intrepid McDonalds-maker first went to the store and purchased all the necessary ingredients: hamburger buns, ground beef, cheese slices, pickles, onions, mustard, ketchup, and sesame seeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Rose Does in This Photo - You Have to See It To Believe It!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-rose-does-in-this-photo-you-have-to-see-it-to-believe-it-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-rose-does-in-this-photo-you-have-to-see-it-to-believe-it-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Rose Does in This Photo - You Have to See It To Believe It! Rose has been known for her daring and unique style, but this photo takes the cake It&amp;rsquo;s a picture of Rose standing in a field, with a wild horse galloping around her It&amp;rsquo;s an image of beauty and grace, with Rose&amp;rsquo;s flowing dress and the horse&amp;rsquo;s powerful movements
Details of the Photo The photo captures the moment perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened to Homer on His Worst Day Yet!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-to-homer-on-his-worst-day-yet-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-to-homer-on-his-worst-day-yet-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Homer Simpson is one of the most beloved cartoon characters of all time He&amp;rsquo;s been the star of the hit show, The Simpsons, since 1989 But on one particular day, Homer had a day so bad that it was unforgettable Here&amp;rsquo;s the story of Homer&amp;rsquo;s worst day yet
Overview of Homer&amp;rsquo;s Worst Day Homer&amp;rsquo;s worst day started off innocently enough. He had a job at the nuclear power plant and was just going about his day as usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Caillou&#39;s Daddy Isn&#39;t Home - Read the Full Book Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-caillou-s-daddy-isn-t-home-read-the-full-book-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-caillou-s-daddy-isn-t-home-read-the-full-book-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and exciting book for your child to read? Look no further than You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When Caillou&amp;rsquo;s Daddy Isn&amp;rsquo;t Home This delightful story follows Caillou, a four-year-old boy, as he navigates life without his father at home Caillou experiences a wide range of emotions, from loneliness and sadness to joy and adventure With the help of his mother and grandparents, Caillou learns to cope with his father&amp;rsquo;s absence and discovers the magic of his own imagination</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Hilarious Meme Will Have You Saying &#39;We Have a Girlfriend at Home!&#39; </title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-hilarious-meme-will-have-you-saying-we-have-a-girlfriend-at-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-hilarious-meme-will-have-you-saying-we-have-a-girlfriend-at-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;ve been on the internet lately, you&amp;rsquo;ve probably seen the latest viral meme that has everyone talking It&amp;rsquo;s a funny image of a couple at a restaurant with the caption &amp;ldquo;We have a girlfriend at home!&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a great way to lighten the mood and make people laugh, and it&amp;rsquo;s quickly become one of the most popular memes of the year
Definition of a Meme A meme is a type of image or video that has been widely shared on the internet It usually contains a funny or clever caption, and it often goes viral, meaning it is shared by a lot of people Memes can be used to make a statement, express an opinion, or just to make people laugh</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You See This Hilarious Patrick Homer Meme!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-see-this-hilarious-patrick-homer-meme-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-see-this-hilarious-patrick-homer-meme-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Are you looking for a good laugh? Look no further than the Patrick Homer meme! This hilarious meme has been making people laugh all over the internet, and it&amp;rsquo;s sure to bring a smile to your face too
II Description of Patrick Homer Meme The Patrick Homer meme features a still image of Homer Simpson from the popular animated sitcom The Simpsons. In the image, Homer is wearing a Hawaiian shirt and a pair of sunglasses, and he has a huge smile on his face.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When Caillou&#39;s Daddy Wasn&#39;t Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-caillou-s-daddy-wasn-t-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-caillou-s-daddy-wasn-t-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Caillou is a beloved children’s character who has been entertaining and educating kids for years He is a four-year-old boy who lives with his parents and little sister He loves to explore and learn new things, and his family is always there to support him But recently, something unexpected happened when Caillou’s daddy wasn’t home
What Happened When Caillou’s Daddy Wasn’t Home?
When Caillou’s daddy had to travel away from home for a few days, Caillou was not happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When This Person Sees the &#39;Let&#39;s Go Home&#39; Meme!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-person-sees-the-let-s-go-home-meme-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-this-person-sees-the-let-s-go-home-meme-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction We&amp;rsquo;ve all seen the &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Home&amp;rdquo; meme It&amp;rsquo;s a simple image of a person looking relieved and excited, with the phrase &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Home!&amp;rdquo; written across the bottom The meme has become a popular way to express relief and excitement, but what happens when someone actually sees the meme in real life?
Background of the Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Home Meme The &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Go Home&amp;rdquo; meme has been around for several years, and it has become a popular way for people to express their relief and excitement about returning home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Homer Falls Asleep - This Hilarious Meme Will Have You Rolling!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-homer-falls-asleep-this-hilarious-meme-will-have-you-rolling-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-homer-falls-asleep-this-hilarious-meme-will-have-you-rolling-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A meme is a funny, often viral, image or video that is shared widely on social media It usually has a humorous caption or message that is meant to be shared with others The Homer Falling Asleep meme is one of the most popular memes of the past few years
Definition of a Meme A meme is an image, video, or phrase that is shared widely online. It typically has a humorous message or caption that is meant to be shared with others.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
