<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Drama on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/drama/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drama on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/drama/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens in Home After Dark Season 3!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-in-home-after-dark-season-3-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-in-home-after-dark-season-3-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Are you a fan of the hit Netflix series Home After Dark? If so, you won&amp;rsquo;t want to miss the upcoming season three, which promises to be even more thrilling than the first two! With new characters and plot twists, this season promises to keep viewers on the edge of their seats
II Plot Summary The third season of Home After Dark picks up with the main character, a teenage boy named Jonah, who has been living with his father in a small town Jonah is trying to figure out who he is and where he belongs in the world As he navigates his way through his new home, he discovers secrets about the town and its residents</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened On the Latest Episode of &#39;A Place To Call Home&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-on-the-latest-episode-of-a-place-to-call-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-on-the-latest-episode-of-a-place-to-call-home-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happened On the Latest Episode of &amp;lsquo;A Place To Call Home&amp;rsquo;! A Place To Call Home is a popular Australian drama series that follows the lives of the Bligh family and their friends in the fictional town of Inverness The show has gained a loyal following over the years, with viewers eagerly awaiting each new episode
Overview of the Main Plot Points The latest episode of A Place To Call Home was a dramatic one, with a number of twists and turns.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
