<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Paper Folding on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/paper-folding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Paper Folding on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/paper-folding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Change the Way You Fold an Aeroplane Forever!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-fold-an-aeroplane-forever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-change-the-way-you-fold-an-aeroplane-forever-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Folding an aeroplane is a classic pastime that has been enjoyed by kids and adults alike for generations But, have you ever wished there was an easier way to fold an aeroplane? Well, we’ve got good news for you! We’ve discovered a simple trick that will change the way you fold an aeroplane forever!
Definition of Folding an Aeroplane Folding an aeroplane is the process of taking a flat sheet of paper and folding it into a 3-dimensional object that resembles an aeroplane.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make You the Champion of Paper Plane Folding!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-the-champion-of-paper-plane-folding-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-you-the-champion-of-paper-plane-folding-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Paper plane folding is a fun and creative activity that has been enjoyed by children and adults alike for generations With the right technique, you can make a paper plane that flies farther and faster than your competitors’ In this blog post, we’ll share a simple trick that will help you become a champion paper plane folder
Overview of Paper Plane Folding Paper plane folding is an art form that requires patience and practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Incredible Trick to Fold an Airplane Out of Paper!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-trick-to-fold-an-airplane-out-of-paper-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-trick-to-fold-an-airplane-out-of-paper-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Folding an Airplane Out of Paper Have you ever wanted to make your own airplane out of paper? It&amp;rsquo;s easier than you think! Folding an airplane out of paper is a fun and creative activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explain the basics of folding an airplane out of paper and provide step-by-step instructions so you can make your own</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
