<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Albion on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/albion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Albion on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/albion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened at Ingram Meridith Funeral Home in Albion, IL!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-ingram-meridith-funeral-home-in-albion-il-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-ingram-meridith-funeral-home-in-albion-il-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s hard to believe what happened at Ingram Meridith Funeral Home in Albion, IL Recently, a video of a funeral home employee mistreating a corpse went viral, causing outrage and shock throughout the community In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll look at the background of the incident, the details of the incident, and the aftermath of the incident
Background of the Incident Ingram Meridith Funeral Home is a family-owned business that has been serving the Albion, IL area since 180.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Happening at Levander Funeral Home in Albion, NE!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-levander-funeral-home-in-albion-ne-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-levander-funeral-home-in-albion-ne-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Levander Funeral Home in Albion, NE Levander Funeral Home in Albion, NE is a family-owned and operated funeral home that has been serving the community since 1936 This long-standing business has been providing funeral services to families in the area for generations, and continues to provide a high level of care and professionalism
Overview of the Unique Services at Levander Funeral Home At Levander Funeral Home, they understand that each funeral service is unique and special.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
