<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Community&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking Loss: Read the Obituaries of Those Who Have Passed Away at Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-loss-read-the-obituaries-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-phillips-and-luckey-funeral-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-loss-read-the-obituaries-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-phillips-and-luckey-funeral-home/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home, located in Austin, Texas, has been serving families since 1894 The funeral home provides a variety of services to families who have lost a loved one, including funeral and memorial services, cremation services, and pre-planning In addition, Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home also offers obituaries for those who have passed away
Overview of the Obituaries The obituaries published by Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home provide an opportunity for families and friends to remember and honor their loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking News: Lufkin Community Mourns as Carroway Funeral Home Releases Obituaries</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Lufkin community was recently devastated by the heartbreaking news that Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries of those that had passed away. This news has left a deep impact on the community, as many of the deceased were well-known and loved members of the Lufkin community.
Overview of the heartbreaking news The Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries for those that had passed away in the Lufkin community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Small-Town Funeral Home in Eden, NC is Doing to Help Families</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-small-town-funeral-home-in-eden-nc-is-doing-to-help-families/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-small-town-funeral-home-in-eden-nc-is-doing-to-help-families/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What This Small-Town Funeral Home in Eden, NC is Doing to Help Families The small-town of Eden, NC is home to a funeral home that is doing something extraordinary to help families With the help of their compassionate and caring staff, this funeral home is going above and beyond to provide the families they serve with personalized services and support during their time of need
Introduction Located in the heart of Eden, NC, this small-town funeral home is providing families with services that go beyond the traditional funeral services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
