<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Merchandise&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/merchandise/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Merchandise&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/merchandise/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Solange Just Dropped: Get Your Hands on the When I Get Home Vinyl Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-solange-just-dropped-get-your-hands-on-the-when-i-get-home-vinyl-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-solange-just-dropped-get-your-hands-on-the-when-i-get-home-vinyl-now-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Solange, the Grammy-winning singer-songwriter and artist, just dropped her highly anticipated When I Get Home vinyl! The When I Get Home vinyl is a limited edition release that features unique artwork, high-quality sound, and is sure to be a collector&amp;rsquo;s item
Background of Solange Solange is a critically acclaimed artist who has been making waves in the music industry since the early 2000s. She has released five studio albums, with her latest being the critically acclaimed When I Get Home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Just Been Released In The UK: Spider Man No Way Home Merch!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-just-been-released-in-the-uk-spider-man-no-way-home-merch-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-just-been-released-in-the-uk-spider-man-no-way-home-merch-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction It&amp;rsquo;s been a long wait, but it&amp;rsquo;s finally here: the much anticipated release of Spider Man: No Way Home merchandise in the UK Fans of the Marvel Cinematic Universe and Spider Man have been eagerly awaiting the release of this merchandise, and now they can finally get their hands on it
Overview of Spider Man: No Way Home Spider Man: No Way Home is the third installment in the Spider Man trilogy, and it&amp;rsquo;s set to be released in theaters in December 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Just Released - Get Your Merch Now and &#39;How You Like That&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-released-get-your-merch-now-and-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-just-released-get-your-merch-now-and-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Blackpink is a popular K-pop girl group that has been making waves in the music industry since their debut in 2016 The group consists of four members, Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa, and is managed by YG Entertainment They have released several hit singles and albums, and have gained a huge following around the world
Recently, Blackpink has released some amazing new merchandise and a brand new single, ‘How You Like That’.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
