<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fashion on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/fashion/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Fashion on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/fashion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink&#39;s Rose Looks Like In This Photo!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-s-rose-looks-like-in-this-photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-s-rose-looks-like-in-this-photo-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Hello everyone! We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of the amazing South Korean girl group, Blackpink They&amp;rsquo;ve taken the world by storm with their incredible music and visuals Today, we&amp;rsquo;re going to be talking about one of their members, Rose We recently stumbled upon a photo of her and we just had to share it with all of you!
II Overview of Blackpink and Rose Blackpink is a four-member South Korean girl group under YG Entertainment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What the Milan Home Kit for 2023 Looks Like!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-the-milan-home-kit-for-2023-looks-like-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-the-milan-home-kit-for-2023-looks-like-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you a fan of AC Milan? If so, then you&amp;rsquo;re in for a treat! The Milan Home Kit for 2023 has been unveiled and it looks absolutely stunning From the colors to the design, this is a kit that is sure to turn heads Let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at what the Milan Home Kit for 2023 has to offer
Design of the Milan Home Kit for 2023 The Milan Home Kit for 2023 is a classic black and red design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Timeless Ways to Master Elegant Style and Look Amazing!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/5-timeless-ways-to-master-elegant-style-and-look-amazing-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/5-timeless-ways-to-master-elegant-style-and-look-amazing-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Elegance is timeless It’s the kind of style that never goes out of fashion, and it’s the kind of look that will always be admired It’s the kind of style that you can take with you wherever you go and always look amazing But mastering elegant style isn’t always easy To help you out, here are five timeless ways to master elegant style and look amazing!
Defining Elegant Style Elegant style is all about looking polished, sophisticated, and put-together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When She Put On That Bucket Hat!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-put-on-that-bucket-hat-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-she-put-on-that-bucket-hat-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Bucket hats have been around for decades, but they&amp;rsquo;ve recently become a popular fashion trend From celebrities to everyday people, everyone is trying out the trend But what happens when someone decides to take the plunge and wear a bucket hat for the first time?
Background Information Bucket hats have been around since the early 100s, but they weren&amp;rsquo;t popular until the 180s. Since then, they&amp;rsquo;ve been seen on everyone from hip-hop artists to college students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG! You Won&#39;t Believe What Jennie from Blackpink Looks Like In Her Latest &#39;How You Like That&#39; Photo!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/omg-you-won-t-believe-what-jennie-from-blackpink-looks-like-in-her-latest-how-you-like-that-photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/omg-you-won-t-believe-what-jennie-from-blackpink-looks-like-in-her-latest-how-you-like-that-photo-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Jennie from Blackpink is one of the most popular K-Pop idols today, and her latest &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; photo has been making waves all over the world! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at the background of Jennie, the details of her latest photo, and the reactions it has received
Background of Jennie from Blackpink Jennie Kim, also known by her stage name Jennie, is a South Korean singer and songwriter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>maskYou Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When Nino Wore His Home Face Mask!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/maskyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-nino-wore-his-home-face-mask-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/maskyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-nino-wore-his-home-face-mask-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Nino was a young man living in the city who had recently purchased a home face mask He was excited to try it out and see what kind of reaction he would get from the people he encountered Little did he know that his experience wearing the mask would be far more than he ever expected
Background of Nino and the Face Mask Nino was a twenty-something year old man who had recently moved to the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OMG! You Won&#39;t Believe What Blackpink Lisa Looks Like In This How You Like That Photo!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/omg-you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-lisa-looks-like-in-this-how-you-like-that-photo-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/omg-you-won-t-believe-what-blackpink-lisa-looks-like-in-this-how-you-like-that-photo-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction A Background Information: Blackpink is a South Korean girl group formed by YG Entertainment The group consists of four members: Jisoo, Jennie, Rosé, and Lisa Blackpink has become one of the most successful K-pop groups in the world, with their most recent single, “How You Like That,” becoming a huge hit
B. Thesis Statement: The photo of Blackpink Lisa in the “How You Like That” video has become iconic, and her look has had a major impact on the K-pop scene.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What AC Milan&#39;s New Jersey for 2023 Looks Like!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-ac-milan-s-new-jersey-for-2023-looks-like-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-ac-milan-s-new-jersey-for-2023-looks-like-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Football fans around the world are in for a treat AC Milan, one of the most storied clubs in the world, has just unveiled their new jersey for the 2023 season This new jersey is sure to turn heads and have fans clamoring for more Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at what makes this jersey so special
II Design Elements of the Jersey The new jersey is a modern take on the classic AC Milan look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Add Pink to Your Look - How You Like That!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-add-pink-to-your-look-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-add-pink-to-your-look-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Add Pink to Your Look - How You Like That! Introduction Pink is a beautiful and vibrant color that can instantly add a touch of femininity and glamour to any look. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re trying to make a statement or just want to add a little something extra to your look, adding pink can be a great way to do it. In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the benefits of adding pink to your look, as well as some ways to incorporate it into your wardrobe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Manoban Just Dropped Something Unexpected and We&#39;re LOVING It - How You Like That?!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lisa-manoban-just-dropped-something-unexpected-and-we-re-loving-it-how-you-like-that-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lisa-manoban-just-dropped-something-unexpected-and-we-re-loving-it-how-you-like-that-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lisa Manoban, better known as Lisa of the K-pop girl group BLACKPINK, has just dropped something unexpected and fans are absolutely loving it! In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at who Lisa is, what this unexpected thing is, and how fans are reacting
Who is Lisa Manoban? Lisa Manoban is a Thai singer, dancer, and rapper who is part of the K-pop girl group BLACKPINK. She is known for her powerful and charismatic performances, as well as her stunning visuals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Little It Costs to Look Good in Russell Athletic Harga!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-little-it-costs-to-look-good-in-russell-athletic-harga-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-little-it-costs-to-look-good-in-russell-athletic-harga-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Russell Athletic Harga Are you looking for a great place to shop for quality apparel at an affordable price? Look no further than Russell Athletic Harga! Russell Athletic Harga is a popular clothing store specializing in sportswear, activewear, and casualwear With a wide selection of styles and sizes, Russell Athletic Harga is the perfect place to find the perfect look for any occasion
Benefits of Shopping at Russell Athletic Harga Not only does Russell Athletic Harga offer a great selection of apparel, but they also offer great customer service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
