<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Tricks and Pranks on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/tricks-and-pranks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tricks and Pranks on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/tricks-and-pranks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Incredible Paper Aeroplane Trick!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-aeroplane-trick-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-aeroplane-trick-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever tried to make a paper aeroplane? It&amp;rsquo;s a fun activity that can be enjoyed by both children and adults alike Paper aeroplanes are a great way to pass the time, and they can also be used for some pretty impressive tricks In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a look at an incredible paper aeroplane trick, and how you can do it yourself
Definition of Paper Aeroplane A paper aeroplane is a simple toy made from a sheet of paper that is folded and twisted into a variety of shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Amazing Paper Airplane Trick!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-amazing-paper-airplane-trick-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-amazing-paper-airplane-trick-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Amazing Paper Airplane Trick! Are you looking for an exciting and fun way to pass the time? If so, then you must try this amazing paper airplane trick With just a few simple materials and some basic folding techniques, you can make a plane that can fly for miles!
Overview of the Paper Airplane Trick This paper airplane trick is simple, but it does require some effort.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
