<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Events on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community-events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community Events on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community-events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Witness the Heartwarming Farewell of a Lifelong Community Member at Gramm Funeral Home in Ipswich, SD</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/witness-the-heartwarming-farewell-of-a-lifelong-community-member-at-gramm-funeral-home-in-ipswich-sd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/witness-the-heartwarming-farewell-of-a-lifelong-community-member-at-gramm-funeral-home-in-ipswich-sd/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Gramm Funeral Home in Ipswich, SD recently held a heartwarming ceremony in honor of a lifelong community member The event was filled with music, readings, and heartfelt words from friends and family This blog post will provide an overview of Gramm Funeral Home, Ipswich, SD, and the ceremony details
Overview of Gramm Funeral Home Gramm Funeral Home has been an integral part of the Ipswich, SD community for over 40 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Happening at Broadview Heights Home Days!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-broadview-heights-home-days-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-broadview-heights-home-days-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Broadview Heights Home Days! It&amp;rsquo;s the most exciting time of the year in our city and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to show you all the amazing events and activities that are happening this year From live music to carnival rides, there&amp;rsquo;s something for every age and interest So come join us for a weekend of fun and excitement!
Events and Activities This year&amp;rsquo;s Home Days will be bigger and better than ever!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Happening at Down Home Days Chickamauga GA in 2022!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-down-home-days-chickamauga-ga-in-2022-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-happening-at-down-home-days-chickamauga-ga-in-2022-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Down Home Days Chickamauga GA in 2022 Down Home Days Chickamauga GA in 2022 is an annual event that celebrates the history and culture of the Chickamauga GA community This year, the event is taking place on June 24th and 2th and promises to be a weekend of fun and excitement for all From a parade to a car show, and from a carnival to a craft fair, there is something for everyone to enjoy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience a Blast from the Past at Old Home Days in Hudson, NH!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/experience-a-blast-from-the-past-at-old-home-days-in-hudson-nh-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/experience-a-blast-from-the-past-at-old-home-days-in-hudson-nh-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun, family-friendly event to attend this summer? Look no further than Old Home Days in Hudson, NH! Old Home Days is an annual event that celebrates the town’s history and heritage It’s a great way to experience a blast from the past while making lasting memories with your loved ones
Overview of Old Home Days in Hudson, NH Old Home Days is a three-day event that takes place in the heart of Hudson, NH It includes a variety of activities such as a parade, live music, carnival rides, a craft fair, and more The event is a great way to learn about the history of the town and the people who have lived there for generations</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
