<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pop Music on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/pop-music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pop Music on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/pop-music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Uplifting Song Will Have You Singing &#39;Welcome Home&#39; in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-uplifting-song-will-have-you-singing-welcome-home-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-uplifting-song-will-have-you-singing-welcome-home-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome Home is an uplifting song that has been embraced by many people around the world It has become a popular anthem for those who are feeling lost, lonely, and disconnected This song has a powerful message and has been used to bring people together in times of hardship
Background of the Song Welcome Home was written by singer-songwriter John Hill and was released in 201. The song was inspired by Hill&amp;rsquo;s own struggles with depression and anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>lineupYou Won&#39;t Believe Who&#39;s Coming to Home Festival 2022 - Check Out the Amazing Artist Lineup!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lineupyou-won-t-believe-who-s-coming-to-home-festival-2022-check-out-the-amazing-artist-lineup-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lineupyou-won-t-believe-who-s-coming-to-home-festival-2022-check-out-the-amazing-artist-lineup-/</guid>
      <description>Home Festival 2022: An Unforgettable Lineup Home Festival 2022 is just around the corner and the lineup is truly something to behold From headliners to supporting acts, the artist lineup is sure to make this one of the most memorable festivals of the year Keep reading to find out who’s coming to Home Festival 2022 and why you won’t want to miss it
Overview of Home Festival Home Festival is an annual music and arts festival held in the heart of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lalisa Manoban&#39;s New Song &#39;How You Like That&#39; Will Leave You Speechless!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lalisa-manoban-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-will-leave-you-speechless-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/lalisa-manoban-s-new-song-how-you-like-that-will-leave-you-speechless-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lalisa Manoban, also known as Lisa, is a Thai singer and dancer who is part of the K-Pop group BLACKPINK On June 26th, 2020, she released her solo single, &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo;, which has been met with critical acclaim and commercial success This song is sure to leave you speechless!
Overview of Lalisa Manoban&amp;rsquo;s Song &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; The song &amp;lsquo;How You Like That&amp;rsquo; is an upbeat and energetic track that is sure to get you on your feet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Song Will Make You Feel Like You&#39;re Home: Listen to &#39;Tell Me If You Wanna Go Home&#39; Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-song-will-make-you-feel-like-you-re-home-listen-to-tell-me-if-you-wanna-go-home-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-song-will-make-you-feel-like-you-re-home-listen-to-tell-me-if-you-wanna-go-home-now-/</guid>
      <description>This Song Will Make You Feel Like You&amp;rsquo;re Home: Listen to &amp;lsquo;Tell Me If You Wanna Go Home&amp;rsquo; Now! We all have those days when we just want to be in the comfort of our own home Whether it&amp;rsquo;s after a long day of work, or a stressful period of life, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing quite like being in a place that makes you feel safe and secure
But what if you could feel the same way without actually being in your home?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
