<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Food on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/food/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Food on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/food/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>pizzaYou&#39;ll Never Believe What Happened When We Tried This Frozen Pizza!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/pizzayou-ll-never-believe-what-happened-when-we-tried-this-frozen-pizza-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/pizzayou-ll-never-believe-what-happened-when-we-tried-this-frozen-pizza-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pizza is a beloved dish enjoyed by people all around the world Whether it’s a classic Italian-style pizza or a modern creation with unique toppings, pizza is always a crowd pleaser But what about frozen pizza? With so many brands and varieties available, it can be hard to know which one is the best To find out, we decided to do a taste test of some of the top frozen pizza brands Read on to find out what happened when we tried this frozen pizza!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When This Person Tried Making McDonalds at Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-making-mcdonalds-at-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-this-person-tried-making-mcdonalds-at-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to recreate McDonalds at home? Well, one brave soul decided to take on the challenge and see if it was possible Read on to find out what happened when they tried to make McDonalds at home!
Steps Taken to Recreate McDonalds at Home The intrepid McDonalds-maker first went to the store and purchased all the necessary ingredients: hamburger buns, ground beef, cheese slices, pickles, onions, mustard, ketchup, and sesame seeds.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
