<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Community Service on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community-service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Community Service on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/community-service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Mcminnville Funeral Home Is Doing To Serve The Community!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-mcminnville-funeral-home-is-doing-to-serve-the-community-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-mcminnville-funeral-home-is-doing-to-serve-the-community-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to the Mcminnville Funeral Home The Mcminnville Funeral Home has been serving the people of Mcminnville and the surrounding area since 1881 The Funeral Home has been a fixture of the community for generations, providing a place of comfort and solace for those who have lost a loved one
Overview of the Services They Provide The Mcminnville Funeral Home offers a wide range of services, from traditional funerals to cremations and memorial services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Maryland Funeral Home is Doing to Honor the Deceased</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-maryland-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-deceased/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-maryland-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-deceased/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Death is an inevitable part of life, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be a sorrowful experience A Maryland funeral home is making it their mission to honor the deceased in a unique and meaningful way
II Overview of Funeral Home&amp;rsquo;s Innovative Practices The funeral home, located in the Maryland suburbs of Washington, D.C., offers a variety of services to make the funeral experience more meaningful and personal. They offer a wide range of options, from traditional burial services to unique and creative options such as releasing butterflies, scattering ashes in a special location, and even planting a tree in memory of the deceased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Tremonton, Utah is Doing to Help Families Say Goodbye</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-tremonton-utah-is-doing-to-help-families-say-goodbye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-tremonton-utah-is-doing-to-help-families-say-goodbye/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Tremonton, Utah is a small town located in the northern part of the state It is a close-knit community that prides itself on its tradition of helping families in times of need One funeral home in Tremonton is taking this commitment to the next level by offering unique services that are helping families say goodbye in a meaningful way
Unique Services Offered by the Funeral Home The funeral home in Tremonton is offering a variety of services that are making it easier for families to commemorate their loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Pontiac, IL Just Did!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-pontiac-il-just-did-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-pontiac-il-just-did-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Pontiac, IL Just Did! Pontiac, IL is a small town located in Livingston County It is home to a population of around 10,000 people, and is known for its rural charm and friendly atmosphere Recently, a funeral home in Pontiac, IL has made headlines for its unique and generous offerings to the community
Introduction Pontiac, IL is a small town located in Livingston County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Abbeville SC Just Did!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-abbeville-sc-just-did-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-abbeville-sc-just-did-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Abbeville SC Just Did! I Introduction
Recently, a funeral home in Abbeville SC did something incredibly generous and unexpected This act of kindness has been making waves in the community and is an example of how small businesses can make a big difference
A. Background of the Funeral Home in Abbeville SC
The funeral home, located in Abbeville SC, has been in business for over 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Local Funeral Home is Doing to Honor the Lives of Those Who Have Passed</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-local-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-lives-of-those-who-have-passed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-local-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-lives-of-those-who-have-passed/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The loss of a loved one can be a difficult and heartbreaking experience But one local funeral home is doing something special to honor the lives of those who have passed
Services Offered by the Funeral Home The funeral home is offering a unique service to families who have lost a loved one. They are providing personalized memorial services that are tailored to the life of the deceased. This includes providing a personalized video tribute, creating a custom memorial website, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Small Town Funeral Home is Doing to Help Families in Need!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-small-town-funeral-home-is-doing-to-help-families-in-need-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-small-town-funeral-home-is-doing-to-help-families-in-need-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In times of need, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a strong support system For families in one small town, that support system includes a funeral home that is going above and beyond to help those in need
Overview of the Funeral Home The funeral home in question is located in a small rural town in the Midwest. It is family owned and operated, and has been in business for over 50 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Funeral Home in Anderson, SC Is Doing to Honor the Deceased!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-anderson-sc-is-doing-to-honor-the-deceased-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-funeral-home-in-anderson-sc-is-doing-to-honor-the-deceased-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Overview of the Funeral Home in Anderson, SC The funeral home in Anderson, SC is doing something truly special to honor the deceased Located in the heart of Anderson, SC, this funeral home has been providing services to families in the area for years They are now taking things a step further by providing an opportunity to honor the memory of the deceased in a unique and meaningful way</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
