<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Funeral Home Stories on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/funeral-home-stories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Funeral Home Stories on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/funeral-home-stories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened at the W.B. Crumel Funeral Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-the-w-b-crumel-funeral-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-the-w-b-crumel-funeral-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The WB Crumel Funeral Home in rural Georgia was the scene of an incredible event last month What started as a typical day of honoring a loved one ended with a shocking surprise In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the details of this incredible incident and the aftermath of the event
Background Information The WB Crumel Funeral Home has been a staple of this small community for over 50 years It has been the site of hundreds of funerals, and it has been the source of comfort for countless families On the day of the incident, the funeral home was hosting a service for a beloved community member</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened at Eckler Hudson Funeral Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-eckler-hudson-funeral-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-eckler-hudson-funeral-home-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction We&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of the Eckler Hudson Funeral Home, but few of us know the story of what happened there It&amp;rsquo;s a tale of a family that came together to celebrate the life of a loved one, only to have the event turn into something truly special This is the story of the Eckler Hudson Funeral Home
II The Events at the Funeral Home The family of the deceased had gathered to pay their respects at the funeral home, when something truly remarkable happened.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
