<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Grammar&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/grammar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Grammar&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/grammar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are You Making This Common Mistake When You Spell &#39;Honey&#39;? Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-common-mistake-when-you-spell-honey-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/are-you-making-this-common-mistake-when-you-spell-honey-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you making a common mistake when you spell &amp;lsquo;honey&amp;rsquo;? If so, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone! Many people make the same mistake when they try to spell this sweet word In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll take a closer look at the common mistakes when spelling &amp;lsquo;honey&amp;rsquo; and offer some tips on how to avoid making them in the future
Overview of the Common Mistake When Spelling &amp;lsquo;Honey&amp;rsquo; When it comes to spelling &amp;lsquo;honey&amp;rsquo;, many people make the mistake of adding an &amp;rsquo;e&amp;rsquo;, an &amp;lsquo;i&amp;rsquo;, or an &amp;lsquo;o&amp;rsquo; instead of the correct &amp;lsquo;y&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know The Right Way To Spell Muesli? Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-right-way-to-spell-muesli-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-right-way-to-spell-muesli-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>What is Muesli? Muesli is a type of cereal made from a combination of raw rolled oats, nuts, fruits and seeds It is usually served as a breakfast cereal with milk or yogurt, but it can also be eaten as a snack or as part of a meal The name muesli comes from the German word “mues” which means “mixture”
History of Muesli Muesli was first developed in 1900 by Swiss doctor Maximilian Bircher-Benner as a nutritious meal for his patients He believed that eating a combination of raw fruits, nuts, and grains was the best way to maintain optimal health Since then, muesli has become a popular breakfast cereal around the world</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know the Right Way to Spell &#39;Council&#39;? Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-right-way-to-spell-council-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-right-way-to-spell-council-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you know the right way to spell the word &amp;lsquo;council&amp;rsquo;? Many people struggle with this word due to its various spellings In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the different spellings of &amp;lsquo;council&amp;rsquo;, why it matters to spell it correctly, and how to spell it correctly
Definition of Council The word &amp;lsquo;council&amp;rsquo; is a noun that refers to a group of people who come together to discuss and make decisions about something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Know the Secret to Spelling &#39;Armour&#39;? Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-secret-to-spelling-armour-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-know-the-secret-to-spelling-armour-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Spelling &amp;lsquo;Armour&amp;rsquo; Spelling the word &amp;lsquo;armour&amp;rsquo; can be tricky, especially when you consider the different spellings of the word In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the secret to spelling &amp;lsquo;armour&amp;rsquo; correctly
Definition of Armour Armour is a noun that refers to protective clothing, such as a suit of armour or a bulletproof vest. It can also be used to refer to a person or thing that provides protection, such as a shield or a fortress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do You Spell Focussed Wrong? Find Out the Right Way Here!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-spell-focussed-wrong-find-out-the-right-way-here-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/do-you-spell-focussed-wrong-find-out-the-right-way-here-/</guid>
      <description>Do You Spell Focussed Wrong? Find Out the Right Way Here! Have you ever wondered if you were spelling the word &amp;ldquo;focussed&amp;rdquo; correctly? It can be a tricky word to spell because of its similarity to the word &amp;ldquo;focused,&amp;rdquo; but there is a right way to spell it Read on to learn more about the correct spelling of focussed and why it is so often misspelled
I Introduction The word &amp;ldquo;focussed&amp;rdquo; is a verb that means to give attention to or concentrate on something.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
