<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Self-Improvement on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/self-improvement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self-Improvement on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/self-improvement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Nilu&#39;s Amazing Advice: How to Save a Life and Transform Your Own!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/nilu-s-amazing-advice-how-to-save-a-life-and-transform-your-own-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/nilu-s-amazing-advice-how-to-save-a-life-and-transform-your-own-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Hi everyone! My name is Nilu, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to share with you my amazing advice on how to save a life and transform your own! I believe that everyone has the power to make a difference in the world, and I&amp;rsquo;m here to help you do just that In this blog post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing the importance of learning CPR and taking a first aid course, donating blood, developing a positive mindset, setting goals and creating a plan, and taking action and making changes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This One Simple Trick Completely Changed My Life - Find Out How!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-completely-changed-my-life-find-out-how-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-one-simple-trick-completely-changed-my-life-find-out-how-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Do you ever feel like you’re stuck in the same routines and habits, and like you’re not making any progress towards your goals? We all have moments of feeling like we’re stuck in a rut but it doesn’t have to be that way Recently, I discovered a simple trick that has completely changed my life and I’m excited to share it with you today
How This Simple Trick Changed My Life I realized that I was getting stuck in the same patterns of behavior and that I wasn’t making any progress towards the life I wanted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
