<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Videos&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/videos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videos&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/videos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>videoYou Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When Blackpink Dropped Their &#39;How You Like That&#39; Music Video!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/videoyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-blackpink-dropped-their-how-you-like-that-music-video-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/videoyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-blackpink-dropped-their-how-you-like-that-music-video-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Blackpink is one of the most popular K-Pop girl groups in the world, and they recently made a huge splash with their new single, “How You Like That” The music video for the song was released on June 26th, 2020, and it has been met with an overwhelmingly positive reception from fans and critics alike In this blog post, we’ll take a look at the impact of the “How You Like That” music video, and how it has helped to solidify Blackpink’s status as one of the biggest names in K-Pop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Watch This Incredible Paper Airplane Tutorial!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-watch-this-incredible-paper-airplane-tutorial-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-watch-this-incredible-paper-airplane-tutorial-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and creative way to pass the time? Then you should check out this incredible paper airplane tutorial! In this blog post, we will provide an overview of the tutorial, explain why it is worth watching, and provide step-by-step instructions for constructing your very own paper airplane
Overview of Paper Airplane Tutorial This paper airplane tutorial is a fun and interactive way to learn how to make a paper airplane It covers everything from gathering supplies to constructing the paper airplane and adding finishing touches The tutorial is easy to follow and provides detailed instructions for each step of the process</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
