<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Social Impact&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/social-impact/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Social Impact&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/social-impact/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! This Credit Company in Pondok Gede is Changing Lives!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-credit-company-in-pondok-gede-is-changing-lives-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/unbelievable-this-credit-company-in-pondok-gede-is-changing-lives-/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable! This Credit Company in Pondok Gede is Changing Lives! I Introduction
Financial services are integral to achieving economic freedom Unfortunately, many individuals in Pondok Gede, Indonesia, lack access to financial services due to poverty and other socio-economic factors Fortunately, a local credit company is changing the lives of these individuals by providing access to financial services
A. Background
Pondok Gede is a district in Bekasi, West Java, Indonesia. It is home to over 350,000 people, with a large percentage of the population living in poverty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>?Find Out When This Iconic Song Was Released and How It Changed Lives Forever!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/find-out-when-this-iconic-song-was-released-and-how-it-changed-lives-forever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/find-out-when-this-iconic-song-was-released-and-how-it-changed-lives-forever-/</guid>
      <description>Find Out When This Iconic Song Was Released and How It Changed Lives Forever! Music has the power to bring people together and evoke powerful emotions One song that has become a global phenomenon is “Imagine” by John Lennon Released in 1971, the song has become an anthem of hope and peace and has had a lasting impact on the world
Overview of the Song “Imagine” is a simple yet powerful song about peace and unity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
