<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Events&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Miss Out: Experience the Magic of Old Home Days in Williamsville 2022!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-experience-the-magic-of-old-home-days-in-williamsville-2022-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-experience-the-magic-of-old-home-days-in-williamsville-2022-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Old Home Days in Williamsville 2022 Old Home Days is a longstanding tradition in Williamsville, NY Every year, the village celebrates its history and culture with a variety of activities and attractions This year, Old Home Days in Williamsville will take place from June 17th to June 20th, 2022
What is Old Home Days? Old Home Days is a celebration of the history and culture of Williamsville, NY. It is a four-day event that features a variety of activities and attractions, such as parades, street fairs, live music, carnival rides, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Miss Out: Get Your Big Ten Mens Basketball Tournament Tickets Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-get-your-big-ten-mens-basketball-tournament-tickets-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-get-your-big-ten-mens-basketball-tournament-tickets-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you ready for some Big Ten men&amp;rsquo;s basketball? The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is coming up and it&amp;rsquo;s time to get your tickets! This exciting event will take place from March 11-14 in Indianapolis, Indiana at Bankers Life Fieldhouse Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the opportunity to see some of the best college basketball teams in the country compete for the Big Ten championship
Benefits of Attending the Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament The Big Ten Men&amp;rsquo;s Basketball Tournament is a great way to experience the excitement of college basketball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Miss Out: See the Latest Home Trends at the Colorado Springs Home Show!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-see-the-latest-home-trends-at-the-colorado-springs-home-show-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-see-the-latest-home-trends-at-the-colorado-springs-home-show-/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Miss Out: See the Latest Home Trends at the Colorado Springs Home Show! Are you looking to upgrade your home with the latest trends? Look no further than the Colorado Springs Home Show! This yearly event is the perfect place to get inspired and find the perfect products to make your home look and feel its best
Overview of the Colorado Springs Home Show The Colorado Springs Home Show is a one-stop shop for all of your home improvement needs From landscaping to interior design, the show has something for everyone You can find the latest products and services from local businesses and national brands, as well as advice from experienced professionals Plus, there are plenty of fun activities and giveaways to keep you entertained throughout the day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Miss Out on the Once-in-a-Lifetime Opportunity to See Boise&#39;s Parade of Homes 2022!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-on-the-once-in-a-lifetime-opportunity-to-see-boise-s-parade-of-homes-2022-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-on-the-once-in-a-lifetime-opportunity-to-see-boise-s-parade-of-homes-2022-/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t Miss Out on the Once-in-a-Lifetime Opportunity to See Boise&amp;rsquo;s Parade of Homes 2022! The Boise Parade of Homes is a one-of-a-kind event that offers attendees an opportunity to explore the latest in home design, construction, and technology From luxurious custom homes to log cabins, the Parade of Homes provides a unique look into the world of home building This year, the event will take place from June 4th to June 20th</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Miss Out! Boise Home Show 2022 is Coming Soon - Get Ready to Be Inspired!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-boise-home-show-2022-is-coming-soon-get-ready-to-be-inspired-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/don-t-miss-out-boise-home-show-2022-is-coming-soon-get-ready-to-be-inspired-/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Are you looking for inspiration for your next home renovation or remodeling project? Look no further than the Boise Home Show 2022! This annual event is the perfect place to find everything you need to make your next home improvement project a success From exhibitors and activities to seminars and more, the Boise Home Show 2022 is sure to have something for everyone
Reasons to Attend The Boise Home Show 2022 is the perfect opportunity to explore all the latest trends in home improvement, remodeling, and design.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Coming to El Paso: The Home and Garden Show!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-coming-to-el-paso-the-home-and-garden-show-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-coming-to-el-paso-the-home-and-garden-show-/</guid>
      <description>You Won&amp;rsquo;t Believe What&amp;rsquo;s Coming to El Paso: The Home and Garden Show! El Paso is about to get its first Home and Garden Show! This event will be a great opportunity for El Pasoans to get access to the latest products and services in the home and garden industry Here’s everything you need to know about the upcoming Home and Garden Show
Overview of the Home and Garden Show The Home and Garden Show is a one-day event that will take place in El Paso on Saturday, April 17th.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
