<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Memorialization on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/memorialization/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Memorialization on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/memorialization/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Family and Friends Mourn at Dirks Blem Funeral Home - An Obituary to Remember</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/family-and-friends-mourn-at-dirks-blem-funeral-home-an-obituary-to-remember/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/family-and-friends-mourn-at-dirks-blem-funeral-home-an-obituary-to-remember/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dirks Blem Funeral Home is a local funeral home in the community that has been providing funeral services for over 100 years They have a long history of providing compassionate and professional care to families during their time of need Recently, the funeral home was the site of an obituary to remember, as family and friends gathered to mourn the passing of a beloved family member
The Funeral Home and its Services A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Local Funeral Home is Doing to Honor the Lives of Those Who Have Passed</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-local-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-lives-of-those-who-have-passed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-local-funeral-home-is-doing-to-honor-the-lives-of-those-who-have-passed/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The loss of a loved one can be a difficult and heartbreaking experience But one local funeral home is doing something special to honor the lives of those who have passed
Services Offered by the Funeral Home The funeral home is offering a unique service to families who have lost a loved one. They are providing personalized memorial services that are tailored to the life of the deceased. This includes providing a personalized video tribute, creating a custom memorial website, and more.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Stories of Those Who Have Passed Away at Tennant Funeral Home in Bastrop</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-stories-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-tennant-funeral-home-in-bastrop/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-stories-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-tennant-funeral-home-in-bastrop/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Tennant Funeral Home in Bastrop, Texas, has been providing funeral services to families in the area for over 100 years Founded in 1912, the business has been a staple of the community ever since Through the years, they have become renowned for their commitment to providing quality service and care to those who have passed away and their families
History of Tennant Funeral Home Tennant Funeral Home was founded in 112 by John and Mary Tennant.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
