<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>WA&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/wa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WA&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/wa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Live Like Royalty: Incredible Homes For Sale in Castle Rock, WA!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/live-like-royalty-incredible-homes-for-sale-in-castle-rock-wa-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/live-like-royalty-incredible-homes-for-sale-in-castle-rock-wa-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a place to live like royalty? Look no further than Castle Rock, Washington! This small town in Cowlitz County is a hidden gem, offering a wide variety of amenities and features that make it a great place to call home Read on to learn more about what Castle Rock has to offer and the incredible homes for sale in the area!
Features of Castle Rock, WA Castle Rock is a town steeped in history and beauty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Affordable These Homes for Sale in Tieton, WA Are!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-these-homes-for-sale-in-tieton-wa-are-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-affordable-these-homes-for-sale-in-tieton-wa-are-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for an affordable place to call home? If so, then you won&amp;rsquo;t believe how affordable the homes for sale in Tieton, WA are! This small town in the Yakima Valley is a great place to buy a home and start a new life
Overview of Tieton, WA Tieton is a small town in the Yakima Valley of Washington State It is located just east of Yakima and is a great place to live The town has a population of just over 1,000 people, so it is a great place to get away from the hustle and bustle of city life The town is surrounded by stunning mountain views and is close to many outdoor recreation activities</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
