<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Television&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/television/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Television&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/television/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Many Episodes the Korean Version of Money Heist Has!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-many-episodes-the-korean-version-of-money-heist-has-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-many-episodes-the-korean-version-of-money-heist-has-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Money Heist, or La Casa de Papel, is an international sensation It&amp;rsquo;s a Spanish crime drama that has taken the world by storm It premiered on Netflix in 2017 and quickly became one of the streaming service&amp;rsquo;s most-watched series Now, it&amp;rsquo;s been adapted into a Korean version, and you won&amp;rsquo;t believe how many episodes it has!
Overview of Money Heist Money Heist follows a group of criminals who plan and execute a daring heist on the Royal Mint of Spain The show follows the characters as they plan and execute the heist, as well as the consequences of their actions The show has been praised for its complex characters and intense plot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Lena Does in Her New Show &#39;House of Dragon&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lena-does-in-her-new-show-house-of-dragon-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-lena-does-in-her-new-show-house-of-dragon-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Lena Headey is a beloved actress known for her roles in Game of Thrones and The Brothers Grimm Her latest project is the highly-anticipated HBO series House of Dragon, which is set to premiere in 2021 In this show, Lena plays the role of Queen Rhaenyra Targaryen, a powerful and cunning ruler who is determined to reclaim her throne
Lena&amp;rsquo;s Character Lena&amp;rsquo;s character in House of Dragon is a complex and intriguing one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Grey&#39;s Anatomy Revealed About the Inspiration Behind &#39;How to Save a Life&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-grey-s-anatomy-revealed-about-the-inspiration-behind-how-to-save-a-life-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-grey-s-anatomy-revealed-about-the-inspiration-behind-how-to-save-a-life-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy has been a staple of American television for over 15 years The show has captivated audiences with its compelling storylines, memorable characters, and powerful performances One of the show&amp;rsquo;s most iconic moments is the performance of the song &amp;ldquo;How to Save a Life&amp;rdquo; by The Fray The song has become a pop culture classic, but the story behind it is even more powerful
Background on Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy is an American medical drama television series created by Shonda Rhimes The show follows the lives of a group of medical professionals at the fictional Seattle Grace Hospital The show has been praised for its realistic portrayal of medicine, its diverse cast, and its powerful storylines</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Many Episodes &#39;Money Heist Korea&#39; Has - Find Out Now!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-many-episodes-money-heist-korea-has-find-out-now-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-many-episodes-money-heist-korea-has-find-out-now-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you heard of the Korean version of the Spanish drama &amp;lsquo;Money Heist&amp;rsquo;? &amp;lsquo;Money Heist Korea&amp;rsquo; is a Korean drama that tells the story of a group of people who plan and execute a daring heist against a large bank It&amp;rsquo;s a thrilling drama that has audiences hooked from start to finish But how many episodes does &amp;lsquo;Money Heist Korea&amp;rsquo; have? Read on to find out!
Overview of &amp;lsquo;Money Heist Korea&amp;rsquo; Plot Summary &amp;lsquo;Money Heist Korea&amp;rsquo; follows a group of people who plan and execute a daring heist against a large bank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Grey&#39;s Anatomy Meets The Fray&#39;s &#39;How To Save A Life&#39;!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-grey-s-anatomy-meets-the-fray-s-how-to-save-a-life-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-grey-s-anatomy-meets-the-fray-s-how-to-save-a-life-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy is a long-running medical drama that has been on the air since 200 It follows the lives of doctors at a Seattle hospital and their relationships with each other and their patients The Fray is an American rock band that formed in 2002 and is best known for their song &amp;ldquo;How To Save A Life&amp;rdquo; The song is about the struggles of trying to help someone in need and the realization that you can&amp;rsquo;t always save them</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
