<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Science &amp; Technology on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/science-technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Science &amp; Technology on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/science-technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Make Your Paper Airplane Fly Farther Than You Ever Thought Possible!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-make-your-paper-airplane-fly-farther-than-you-ever-thought-possible-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to make a paper airplane that could fly farther than any other? Well, here is a simple trick that will make your paper airplane soar farther than you ever thought possible!
Definition of Paper Airplane A paper airplane is a toy aircraft made from folding a piece of paper. It is an inexpensive and easy way to have fun. Paper airplanes can be made from any type of paper, and all you need is your hands and a few simple supplies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unbelievable! Discover the Secret to Making a Paper Plane That Flies Forever!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/unbelievable-discover-the-secret-to-making-a-paper-plane-that-flies-forever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/unbelievable-discover-the-secret-to-making-a-paper-plane-that-flies-forever-/</guid>
      <description>Unbelievable! Discover the Secret to Making a Paper Plane That Flies Forever! Have you ever wanted to make a paper plane that could fly forever? Well, now you can! With the right materials and a few simple steps, you can make a paper plane that will soar through the air for as long as you want
Introduction Making paper planes is a fun and easy activity that can be enjoyed by people of all ages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Try This Incredible Paper Airplane Trick!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-airplane-trick-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-try-this-incredible-paper-airplane-trick-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wanted to fly a paper airplane but didn’t know how? Well, you’re in luck! We have a fun and easy paper airplane trick that you can try today!
Background Information Paper airplanes have been around for centuries, with the first recorded use in China during the 2nd century BC. Since then, paper airplanes have been a favorite pastime for children and adults alike.
Purpose of the Trick The purpose of this trick is to teach you how to make a paper airplane that flies farther and faster than any other paper airplane.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
