<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Local History on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/local-history/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Local History on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/local-history/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happened at the W.B. Crumel Funeral Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-the-w-b-crumel-funeral-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happened-at-the-w-b-crumel-funeral-home-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The WB Crumel Funeral Home in rural Georgia was the scene of an incredible event last month What started as a typical day of honoring a loved one ended with a shocking surprise In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the details of this incredible incident and the aftermath of the event
Background Information The WB Crumel Funeral Home has been a staple of this small community for over 50 years It has been the site of hundreds of funerals, and it has been the source of comfort for countless families On the day of the incident, the funeral home was hosting a service for a beloved community member</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What&#39;s Hiding on La Homa Rd in Mission, TX!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-hiding-on-la-homa-rd-in-mission-tx-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-s-hiding-on-la-homa-rd-in-mission-tx-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to La Homa Rd in Mission, TX Located in the heart of Mission, Texas, La Homa Road is one of the most unique and interesting streets in the entire Rio Grande Valley It is full of hidden gems, surprises, and local culture that you won&amp;rsquo;t find anywhere else Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a local or a visitor, La Homa Road is a must-see destination
Overview of Hidden Gems Along La Homa Rd La Homa Road is home to some of the most unique and interesting attractions in the Rio Grande Valley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Heartwarming Legacy of Robarts Funeral Home in Wauchula, FL</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-heartwarming-legacy-of-robarts-funeral-home-in-wauchula-fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/discover-the-heartwarming-legacy-of-robarts-funeral-home-in-wauchula-fl/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Robarts Funeral Home in Wauchula, Florida has been providing compassionate and professional funeral services to the people of Hardee County and its surrounding areas since 197 The funeral home has been a family-owned and operated business for over 70 years, and the Robarts family has built a legacy of care, compassion, and commitment to the community
Overview of Robarts Funeral Home Robarts Funeral Home is dedicated to providing quality and personalized services to families in their time of need The funeral home offers a wide range of services, including traditional funerals, cremations, pre-planning services, and more They also provide a variety of options for memorialization, such as monuments, urns, and other memorial items The staff at Robarts Funeral Home is committed to providing compassionate and professional care to every family they serve</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
