<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aviation on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/aviation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Aviation on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/aviation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Have You Flying Like a Concorde in No Time!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-flying-like-a-concorde-in-no-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-have-you-flying-like-a-concorde-in-no-time-/</guid>
      <description>This Simple Trick Will Have You Flying Like a Concorde in No Time! Have you ever dreamed of flying like a Concorde? Do you want to know how to fly like a pro? If so, this article is for you! We will discuss the benefits of flying like a Concorde, as well as how to achieve Concorde-level flying
Introduction The Concorde is a supersonic transport aircraft developed by Airbus and British Aerospace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe How Far This Plane Flies After You Follow These Simple Folding Instructions!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-plane-flies-after-you-follow-these-simple-folding-instructions-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-how-far-this-plane-flies-after-you-follow-these-simple-folding-instructions-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and creative way to get your plane to fly farther? If so, you won&amp;rsquo;t believe how far it can go after you follow these simple folding instructions!
Overview of the Folding Instructions The folding instructions are designed to help you get the most out of your plane By following these instructions, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to make sure that your plane is properly folded and ready for flight The instructions are easy to follow, and you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to get your plane ready for takeoff in no time</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What This Person Did to Create the Most Incredible Airplane Ever!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-person-did-to-create-the-most-incredible-airplane-ever-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-this-person-did-to-create-the-most-incredible-airplane-ever-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered how airplanes are created? This article looks at the incredible story of one person who managed to create the most incredible airplane ever We&amp;rsquo;ll look at the background of the person, the description of the airplane, the process of creation, the results of the creation, and the future plans for the airplane
Background of the Person The person in question is John Smith, a passionate aviation enthusiast who had a dream of creating the most incredible airplane ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Simple Trick Will Teach You How to Build the Perfect Airplane!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-build-the-perfect-airplane-/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-simple-trick-will-teach-you-how-to-build-the-perfect-airplane-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun and rewarding project to tackle this summer? Building your own airplane is a great way to learn new skills and explore the world of aviation In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide step-by-step instructions on how to build the perfect airplane from scratch So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Overview of the Topic Building your own airplane is a complex task, but it can be broken down into a few manageable steps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
