<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Comedy&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/comedy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Comedy&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/comedy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Homer Simpson Has Done So Far!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-has-done-so-far-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-homer-simpson-has-done-so-far-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Homer Simpson has been a staple of American culture for decades, and his antics have been the source of much entertainment From his legendary donut eating to his failed attempts at being a rock star, Homer has done it all But what you may not know is that Homer has also accomplished some impressive feats, and we’re here to tell you all about them!
II Homer&amp;rsquo;s Accomplishments Homer has achieved some incredible things in his lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When You Watch Home Alone 2 On 123movies!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-watch-home-alone-2-on-123movies-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-you-watch-home-alone-2-on-123movies-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to 12movies 123movies is an online streaming platform where you can watch movies and TV shows for free It has a wide selection of titles from all genres and is a great way to watch your favorite movies and shows
Overview of Home Alone 2 Home Alone 2 is a classic Christmas movie that follows the adventures of a young boy, Kevin McCallister, who gets separated from his family and has to fend for himself in a strange city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens When Rick and Morty Go Far From Home!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-rick-and-morty-go-far-from-home-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-when-rick-and-morty-go-far-from-home-/</guid>
      <description>I Introduction Are you a fan of the hit animated show Rick and Morty? If so, then you know that the show follows the interdimensional adventures of a mad scientist and his grandson Well, you won&amp;rsquo;t believe what happens when Rick and Morty go far from home!
II Rick and Morty&amp;rsquo;s Adventure In the most recent season of Rick and Morty, the two go on a journey far from their home planet, Earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>h rogen movieYou Won&#39;t Believe What Happened When We Watched That Seth Rogen Movie!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/h-rogen-movieyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-watched-that-seth-rogen-movie-/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/h-rogen-movieyou-won-t-believe-what-happened-when-we-watched-that-seth-rogen-movie-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We recently watched a Seth Rogen movie, and we were absolutely blown away It was one of those movies that you just can&amp;rsquo;t stop thinking about after the credits roll It had us laughing, crying, and ultimately, feeling inspired In this blog post, we&amp;rsquo;ll share what happened when we watched that Seth Rogen movie and the impact it had on us
Background Information Seth Rogen is an actor, writer, producer, and director who has appeared in a variety of films, including Knocked Up, Superbad, Pineapple Express, and The Interview.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Won&#39;t Believe What Happens Next: How You Like That</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-how-you-like-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/you-won-t-believe-what-happens-next-how-you-like-that/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction In June 2020, the K-pop girl group BLACKPINK released their single &amp;ldquo;How You Like That,&amp;rdquo; which quickly became a global sensation From its catchy chorus to its powerful music video, the song quickly gained millions of views and streams, becoming one of the most popular songs of the year In this essay, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore the impact of &amp;ldquo;How You Like That&amp;rdquo; on both the group and the culture at large</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
