<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Family&#34; on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family&#34; on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking Loss: Read the Obituaries of Those Who Have Passed Away at Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-loss-read-the-obituaries-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-phillips-and-luckey-funeral-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-loss-read-the-obituaries-of-those-who-have-passed-away-at-phillips-and-luckey-funeral-home/</guid>
      <description>IV Conclusion
Introduction Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home, located in Austin, Texas, has been serving families since 1894 The funeral home provides a variety of services to families who have lost a loved one, including funeral and memorial services, cremation services, and pre-planning In addition, Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home also offers obituaries for those who have passed away
Overview of the Obituaries The obituaries published by Phillips and Luckey Funeral Home provide an opportunity for families and friends to remember and honor their loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Heartbreaking Story of Straghn and Son Funeral Home Will Make You Cry</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-heartbreaking-story-of-straghn-and-son-funeral-home-will-make-you-cry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/this-heartbreaking-story-of-straghn-and-son-funeral-home-will-make-you-cry/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Straghn and Son Funeral Home was a small family-owned business in the small town of Jonesboro, Arkansas The business was founded in the early 1900s by the Straghn family and was a staple in the community for over 100 years The business provided funeral services to the community and was a place of solace and comfort for the families of the deceased
Background of Straghn and Son Funeral Home The Straghn family had a long and storied history in Jonesboro The family had been in the area for generations and had built a reputation for providing quality funeral services to the community The business was passed down from generation to generation, with each generation making improvements and adding new services</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking News: Lufkin Community Mourns as Carroway Funeral Home Releases Obituaries</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Lufkin community was recently devastated by the heartbreaking news that Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries of those that had passed away. This news has left a deep impact on the community, as many of the deceased were well-known and loved members of the Lufkin community.
Overview of the heartbreaking news The Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries for those that had passed away in the Lufkin community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking News: Family Mourns the Loss of Beloved Member in Homer, NY Obituaries</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-family-mourns-the-loss-of-beloved-member-in-homer-ny-obituaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-family-mourns-the-loss-of-beloved-member-in-homer-ny-obituaries/</guid>
      <description>Introduction We are all deeply saddened by the heartbreaking news that a beloved member of our community has passed away in Homer, NY Our thoughts and prayers are with the family and friends of the deceased during this difficult time
Background Information on the Beloved Member The beloved member was an active member of the Homer community and was well-known for their kind and generous spirit. They were a loving parent, partner, and friend and will be deeply missed by all who knew them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience the Joy of Homeownership with this Exciting New Home Sweet Home Video Game!</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/experience-the-joy-of-homeownership-with-this-exciting-new-home-sweet-home-video-game-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/experience-the-joy-of-homeownership-with-this-exciting-new-home-sweet-home-video-game-/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking for a fun way to experience the joy of homeownership? Look no further than Home Sweet Home Video Game! This exciting new video game offers players the opportunity to build and maintain their own dream home while managing their finances and interacting with their neighbors
Overview of Home Sweet Home Video Game Home Sweet Home Video Game is a simulation game that allows players to build and manage their own dream home Players can choose from a variety of home styles and designs, build their own furniture, and customize the interior and exterior of their home The game also offers players the opportunity to manage their finances, pay their bills, and interact with their neighbors</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
