<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Lismahiska</title>
    <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Lismahiska</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lismahiska.github.io/tags/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Heartbreaking News: Lufkin Community Mourns as Carroway Funeral Home Releases Obituaries</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/heartbreaking-news-lufkin-community-mourns-as-carroway-funeral-home-releases-obituaries/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Lufkin community was recently devastated by the heartbreaking news that Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries of those that had passed away. This news has left a deep impact on the community, as many of the deceased were well-known and loved members of the Lufkin community.
Overview of the heartbreaking news The Carroway Funeral Home released a number of obituaries for those that had passed away in the Lufkin community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Say Goodbye to Loved Ones at Banister Funeral Home in Hiawassee, GA: Obituaries and Services Announced</title>
      <link>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/say-goodbye-to-loved-ones-at-banister-funeral-home-in-hiawassee-ga-obituaries-and-services-announced/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lismahiska.github.io/posts/say-goodbye-to-loved-ones-at-banister-funeral-home-in-hiawassee-ga-obituaries-and-services-announced/</guid>
      <description>Say Goodbye to Loved Ones at Banister Funeral Home in Hiawassee, GA Banister Funeral Home is a family-owned and operated funeral home in Hiawassee, Georgia Dedicated to providing compassionate and professional services to the families of our community, we are here to help you say goodbye to your loved ones in a meaningful and respectful way
Overview of Banister Funeral Home At Banister Funeral Home, we strive to provide an atmosphere of comfort and peace for our families We understand that saying goodbye to a loved one can be a difficult time, and we are here to provide the best possible service to help you through this difficult time We offer a variety of services to meet the needs of our families, including traditional funerals, memorial services, and cremations</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
